http://www.endeavoracademy.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Endeavor Academy collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the https://endeavoracademy.com website ("Site").
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. We currently use Google Analytics for this purpose. For more information on Google’s Analytics privacy policies, please visit https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245
Cookie Policy
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent.
We may use cookies to remember User specific data, such as if you have submitted a form or if you have agreed (or not) to our use of cookies on this site. Our Site may contain Third Party Content (eg. Youtube Videos) which may require cookies to work. Disabling cookies in your browser may prevent this functionality.
How we use collected information
Endeavor Academy may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
To run and operate our Site
We may need your information display content on the Site correctly.
To personalize user experience
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve our Site
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
To send periodic emails
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to registrations, subscriptions or donations. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information and data stored on our Site.
Sharing your personal information
We may use third party service providers to help us in sending out newsletters and other subscribed-to emails. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include unsubscribe and subscriber options links at the bottom of each email, or the User may contact us via our Site. We currently use Aweber for sending out emails. To view their Privacy Policy, please visit: https://www.aweber.com/permission.htm
We may use third party service providers to help us in accepting payments. We do not store any credit card or billing information, or process any transactions on our own servers. We currently use Stripe and Paypal for accepting payments. To view Stripe's Privacy Policy, please visit: https://stripe.com/us/privacy To view Paypal's Privacy Policy, please visit: https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full
Changes to this privacy policy
Endeavor Academy has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will update the modification date at the bottom of this privacy policy page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us.
This document was last updated on June 6, 2018
TOP
Privacy Policy
